http://limitstate.com/legal-privacy

YouTube
Documentation:
Legal & Privacy
Legal and Privacy StatementThis World Wide Web Site (the "Site") is operated by  LimitState Ltd. All content on this website is © Copyright of LimitState Ltd unless otherwise stated.Legal1. Intellectual PropertyAll materials within the Site are the intellectual property of LimitState Ltd unless otherwise stated. Such materials may not be copied or reproduced, save to the extent necessary to view the same on-line. However, you may print complete pages of the site to hard copy for your own personal use. Notwithstanding the generality of the foregoing, LimitState Ltd may from time to time give you the opportunity to download documents, executable programs and other utilities from the Site. Such downloads are covered by the LimitState Ltd Terms and Conditions of Download.2. External LinksLinks to external sites are provided as a convenience to users and such sites are not under the control of LimitState Ltd. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement of that site by LimitState Ltd and LimitState Ltd is not responsible for the contents of any linked site or indeed any link contained in a linked site or for any loss or inconvenience arising from the use of such a site.If you would like us to consider removing a link because of inappropriate content, please contact us on  info@limitstate.com3. Accuracy of InformationThis information in this site is intended for members and potential customers of LimitState Ltd and its affiliates. In this regard, it may not be applicable to other jurisdictions. LimitState Ltd will use reasonable endeavours to ensure that the contents of this Site are accurate and up to date. However, LimitState Ltd reserves the right to change information at any time. No reliance should be placed upon any of the statements made within the site, and LimitState Ltd excludes to the fullest extent permitted by law all liability resulting from any such reliance. Notwithstanding the generality of the foregoing, LimitState Ltd excludes to the fullest extent permitted by law all liability resulting from your access to and use of the Site.4. LimitState Ltd Site Terms and Conditions of DownloadAny software that is made available to download from this Site is the copyrighted work of LimitState Ltd and/or its suppliers. Use of the software is governed by the terms of the end user license agreement, if any, which accompanies or is included with the software ("License Agreement"). You may not download or install any Software that is accompanied by or includes a License Agreement unless you have read and accepted the terms of the License Agreement. REPRODUCTION OR REDISTRIBUTION OF THE SOFTWARE IS PROHIBITED EXCEPT AS PROVIDED FOR IN THE APPLICABLE LICENSE AGREEMENT.Privacy5. Data ProtectionLimitState Ltd respects the privacy of every individual who visits this Site, and strictly adheres to the data protection laws in the UK. This Clause 5 outlines our policy in regards to the collection, usage and storage of personal data.Personal DataIn order to process your request for information and / or software through this Site, we must collect personal information from you that are protected by worldwide data protection laws. LimitState Ltd is committed to compliance with all laws. We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we meet the obligations required by country-specific legislation and the EU Directive on Personal Data Privacy. The information collected via this website will be accessible solely to LimitState Ltd and its agents, who have access rights based on a relevant business need to know. Your data may be used for the purpose of personalising our content delivery and services to meet your individual needs, for market research and marketing purposes.If you do not want your personal data stored in our database, please contact us on  info@limitstate.comNote that we do not store credit card details nor do we share customer financial details with any 3rd parties.Non-Personal Identifiable Information Collected AutomaticallyIn some cases, we may collect information about you that is generic in nature and is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site.Who To ContactIf you have previously submitted Personal Data through the Site and would like that information deleted from our records and database, please contact us on  info@limitstate.com. We will use every reasonable efforts to delete this information from our existing files and confirm with you the deletion of your Personal Data.Cancellations6. LimitState Ltd Warranty and Cancellation PolicyLimitState Ltd warrants that Programs will perform in substantial compliance with the User Guide provided by LimitState Ltd when operated in accordance with the supplied instructions and on supported hardware and operating systems.If within 90 days of purchase the Licensee reports to LimitState Ltd in writing, a significant defect, and LimitState Ltd fails to correct it within 90 days of the date the defect is reported, the Licensee may return the Program in its entirety, and LimitState Ltd will refund the licence fee. Refunds will be processed within 30 days.The Licence is granted without further warranty, condition, representation, or other term express or implied relating to the performance, quality or fitness for use of the Program. Except as regards liability for death or personal injury caused by its negligence, LimitState Ltd will not be liable for any loss or damage of any kind, including, without limitation, indirect or consequential loss (including loss of profits) arising out of the use of or inability to use the Program for any reason, including failure or delay by LimitState Ltd in meeting its obligations under the terms and conditions of this Licence.LimitState Ltd does not guarantee that the Program is free of minor errors not materially affecting its performance. The warranties in this clause are in lieu of any condition or warranty express or implied by law as to the quality or fitness for any particular purpose of the Program.
